Guide to the First Congregational Church of Portland records 1849-2016
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Performing and visual arts, 1875-2016; Series M
  - Program for "The Curious Savage", 1952 (Box-folder 69/17)
    Performance by Pacific University players held at First Congregational Church.
  - Dramatic Jamboree programs and ephemera, 1956 (Box-folder 69/18)
    Event staged by Scrooby Club and Pilgrim Hi Fellowship.
  - "Play report" for Dramatic Jamboree, 1956 (Box-folder 69/19)
  - Letter and list of works re Michael Elvestrom exhibit, 1973 March 23 (Box-folder 69/20)
  - "Fascinating Fashions of Fifty-Five" program, 1955 April 27 (Box-folder 69/21)
  - Programs and clipping re Festival of Arts, 1964, 1966 (Box-folder 69/22)
  - Fine Arts Banquet programs, circa 1959-1960 (Box-folder 69/23)
  - Notes of history of Fine Arts Festival, 1983 September 11 (Box-folder 69/24)
  - Letter about and program for "Heritage of Faith", 1961 (Box-folder 69/25)
    Play by Evangeline Moke, produced for church's 110th anniversary celebration.
  - Script for "Heritage of Faith", 1961 (Box-folder 69/26)
  - History - "Notes on Activities and Performances in Visual, Auditory and Performing Arts in First Congregational Church", 1985 July 22 (Box-folder 69/27)
  - "John Brown's Body", 1981-1982 (Box-folder 69/28)
  - Posters for "John Brown's Body", 1982 (Box-folder 112/15)
  - Flyer for marionette workshop, 1985 (Box-folder 69/29)
  - Flyer for Middle East Peace quilt exhibit, 2001 (Box-folder 69/30)
  - Programs, posters, clippings, and ephemera for Music-Art-Drama (MAD) events, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 69/31)
  - "Noye's Fludde", 1974-1975 (Box-folder 69/32)
  - "Noye's Fludde", 1985 (Box-folder 69/33)
  - "Our Town", 1977 (Box-folder 69/34)
  - Park Block Revels, Subseries 1
    Annual performance event held in December from 1972 until the 1990s. Originally named Medieval Winter Revels.
    - Clippings re Park Block Revels, 1974-1992 (Box-folder 69/35)
    - Correspondence - Letter re Portland State University workshop during Park Block Revels, 1986 October31 (Box-folder 69/36)
    - Correspondence - Open thank-you letter following Park Block Revels, 1991 December 14 (Box-folder 69/37)
    - Financial report for 1990 Revels, 1991 March 31 (Box-folder 69/38)
    - History of Park Block Revels, undated (Box-folder 70/1)
    - List of "Neighbors and Friends" for Park Block Revels, 1991 (Box-folder 70/2)
    - Map, 1984 (Box-folder 70/3)
    - Mission statement, 1989 January 12 (Box-folder 70/4)
    - Notices, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 70/5)
    - Posters, maps, and schedules, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 112/16)
    - Poster and calendar for Winterfaire, 1989 (Box-folder 155/1)
      Calendar includes the schedule for 1989 Park Block Revels.
    - Programs, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 70/6)
    - Programs, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 70/7)
    - Programs, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 70/8)
    - Roster of players, 1987 (Box-folder 70/9)
    - Proposed schedule, 1989 (Box-folder 70/10)
    - Suggestions for 1991 Revels (Box-folder 70/11)
  - Performance programs, 1891; 1893 (Box-folder 70/12)
  - Proposed 1972-1973 performances program, 1972 August 31 (Box-folder 70/13)
  - "The Pigeon Roost", 1970 (Box-folder 70/14)
  - Policies regarding art exhibits, circa 1985 (Box-folder 70/15)
  - Flyer and letter re "Righteous Gentiles", 1988 (Box-folder 70/16)
  - Sacred Dance Guild Festival, 1990 (Box-folder 70/17)
  - Programs and ephemera for Scrooby Players performances, 1952; 1959; undated (Box-folder 70/18)
  - Program for "Swan Song (or 'Who Knocked the Deylights Out of Agnes')", circa 1988 (Box-folder 70/19)
  - Program for "The Telling Project", 2009 May (Box-folder 70/20)
  - Third Sunday Concert, Art and Drama series programs, 1971 (Box-folder 70/21)
  - "Titanic 1912: A Musical Night to Remember", 2012 (Box-folder 70/22)
  - "The Unknown Soldier and His Wife", 1986 (Box-folder 70/23)
  - Calendar for "The Unknown Soldier and His Wife", 1986 (Box-folder 112/17)
  - Walker Players records, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 70/24)
  - Correspondence re Walker Players, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 70/25)
  - Programs, clippings and ephemera re Walker Players performances, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 70/26)
  - Script for "While It Was Still Dark", 1957 (Box-folder 70/27)
  - "The Wilderness Journey" exhibit, 2004 (Box-folder 70/28)
  - Program for "The Windmills of Holland", 1922 (Box-folder 70/29)
- Properties and facilities, 1871-2008; Series N
  - Adult Lounge plans, 1955 November 1 (Box-folder Oversize 11)
  - Plans for altar cross, 1947 January (Box-folder Oversize 12)
  - Basement plans, 1986 July (Box-folder Oversize 15)
  - Insurance appraisals, 1957-1963, 1984 (Box-folder 70/30)
  - Appraisal report, 1982 October 22 (Box-folder 70/31)
  - Appraisal of First Congregational Church properties, 1984 June 15 (Box-folder 70/32)
  - Appraisal of First Congregational Church properties, 1989 November 7 (Box-folder 70/33)
  - Historic preservation grant request for bell tower, 1989 January 13 (Box-folder 71/1)
  - Pre-development grant request for bell tower, 1989 December 22 (Box-folder 71/2)
  - Church bell tower rehabilitation study report, 1991 July (Box-folder 71/3)
  - Plans attached to bell tower rehabilitation study report, 1991 July (Box-folder Oversize 16)
  - Flyer for bell tower restoration fundraising, circa 2010 (Box-folder 71/4)
  - Construction of third church building, Subseries 1
    Materials relating to the construction and opening of the church building at SW Park and Madison.
    - Architectural plans (originals), 1893 (Box-folder Oversize 1 - Oversize 2)
    - Architectural plans (copies), 1893 (Box-folder Oversize 3 - Oversize 10)
      Date copies were made unknown.
    - Church Building Society records, 1893-1894 (Box-folder 71/5)
      Additional materials relating to the society located in Series A, Subseries 2.
    - Contract between Reverend T. Eaton Clapp and E. A. Seeley, 1892 September 7 (Box-folder 71/6)
    - Correspondence - Letter from T. Eaton Clapp to Elizabeth Eggert, 1895 February 25 (Box-folder 71/7)
    - Correspondence with Young Men's Bible Class re use of new church building, 1895 (Box-folder 71/8)
    - Address given at cornerstone dedication ceremony, 1891 August 6 (Box-folder 71/9)
      Also includes research file explaining the provenance of the address' text.
    - Program for church building's dedication service, 1895 July 14 (Box-folder 71/10)
    - Planning, supplies, and bills, 1890-1896 (Box-folder 71/11)
    - Requests for use, 1894-1896 (Box-folder 71/12)
  - Broome, Oringdulph, O'Toole, Rudolf, Boles & Associates (B.O.O.R/A) plans, Subseries 2
    - Title sheet, sheets 3.1, 4.1-4.4, 1986 March (Box-folder Oversize 17)
      Includes floor plans for basement, annex, first floor and second floor.
    - Title sheet, sheets 1.1-4.4, 1986 June (Box-folder Oversize 18)
    - Sheets 5.1-7.4, 1986 March (Box-folder Oversize 19)
      Includes ceiling plans, building cross-section, and elevations.
    - Sheets 5.1-7.4, 1986 June (Box-folder Oversize 20)
    - Sheets 8.1-8.7, 1986 March (Box-folder Oversize 21)
      Includes plumbing, heating, and air conditioning plans.
    - Sheets 8.1-8.7, 1986 June (Box-folder Oversize 22)
    - Sheets 9.1-9.6, 1986 March (Box-folder Oversize 23)
      Includes electrical and lighting plans.
    - Sheets 9.1-9.6, 1986 June (Box-folder Oversize 24)
  - Chapel blueprints, 1953 (Box-folder Oversize 25)
  - Copy of chapel blueprints, 1953 (Box-folder Oversize 26)
  - Drawing of planned chapel interior, 1950 (Box-folder 112/17)
  - Chapel floor plan, 1950 December 19 (Box-folder 112/18)
  - Chapel plans, 1953 (Box-folder Oversize 27)
  - Church plans, undated (Box-folder Oversize 28 - Oversize 29)
  - Copy of plans, circa 2004 (Box-folder Oversize 31)
  - Blueprint of east wall, 1937 April 6 (Box-folder 155/3)
  - Electrical plans, 2004 (Box-folder Oversize 32)
  - Correspondence and records re Forest Park Children's Center, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 71/13)
  - Ground floor and lover level plans, 1976-1977 (Box-folder Oversize 33)
  - Hand-drawn plans, circa 1985 (Box-folder Oversize 34)
  - Plan for additional heating, undated (Box-folder 112/19)
  - Highland Church property transfer, 1904 (Box-folder 71/14)
  - Land purchase from Atkinson family, 1871 (Box-folder 71/15)
  - Land purchases and tax petition, 1904 (Box-folder 71/16)
  - Lower level/basement plans, circa 1976 (Box-folder 155/4)
  - Church masterplan, 1984 (Box-folder 71/17)
  - Program for dedicatory service of memorial window, 1906 October 2 (Box-folder 71/18)
  - Research files re memorials (Box-folder 71/19)
  - Research files re memorial windows and memorial room (Box-folder 71/20)
  - Northwest Pilot Project floor plans, 1988 September 27 - December 5 (Box-folder Oversize 37)
  - Northwest Pilot Project, Inc. proposal, 1987 October 7 (Box-folder 71/21)
  - Organ screen plans, 1951 (Box-folder Oversize 40)
  - Plans, 1976 (Box-folder Oversize 38)
  - Church property and City of Portland, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 71/22)
  - Correspondence and memo re opening of Portland Performing Arts Center (Box-folder 71/23)
  - Scrapbook re Portland Performing Arts Center, 1980-1990 (Box-folder Box 148)
  - Portland Center for Performing Arts plans, 1984 July 20 (Box-folder Oversize 39)
  - "Seed ideas and random thoughts regarding Portland Performing Arts Center", 1983 March (Box-folder 71/24)
  - Property sale, 1896 (Box-folder 71/25)
  - Remodels and renovations, Subseries 3
    - Alteration plans, 1951 (Box-folder Oversize 13)
    - Balcony and stairs remodel plans, 2008 (Box-folder Oversize 14)
    - Building renovation, 1986 (Box-folder 72/1)
    - Plans and drawing of new chapel, 1952 November 13 (Box-folder 155/5)
    - New classroom floor plans and storage facility plans, 1956 August 15-17 (Box-folder Oversize 30)
    - Flyer for party to celebrate renovation, 2005 (Box-folder 72/2)
    - Records, correspondence, and ephemera re historic renovation project, 2002 (Box-folder 72/3)
    - Kitchen remodel plans, 1974 (Box-folder Oversize 35)
    - Kitchen remodel, 1980 (Box-folder 72/4)
    - Kitchen remodel plans, 1980 April (Box-folder Oversize 36)
    - Project manual for church remodel plus addendum, 1986 March (Box-folder 72/5)
    - Correspondence and records re sanctuary remodel, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - Correspondence and records re sanctuary remodel, 2003 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - Sanctuary remodel plans, 2004 (Box-folder Oversize 43 - Oversize 45)
    - Chancel and sanctuary renovation design report by Peck Smiley Ettlin, 2001 October 10 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - Report on negotiations with Broome, Oringdulph and Associates, 1984 January 16 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - Report, "The Sanctuary Enhancement Project", 2002 April 28 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - SERA - Contract and bills, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - New storage room addition plans, 1958 November 20 (Box-folder 155/6)
    - Third floor remodel plans, 1985 (Box-folder Oversize 46)
  - Representative plans of various church rooms, circa 1985 (Box-folder Oversize 42)
  - Sanctuary master plan, circa 1984-1985 (Box-folder 72/12)
  - Sanctuary plan, 2004 (Box-folder 112/20)
  - Section drawing, circa 2004 (Box-folder 155/7)
  - Statements of qualification, Subseries 3
    - H & A Construction, 2004 (Box-folder 72/13)
    - Peck Smiley Ettlin, 2002 (Box-folder 72/14)
    - Robertson, Hay & Wallace, 2004 (Box-folder 73/1)
    - SERA, 2002 (Box-folder 73/2)
  - Structural investigation (original copy), 1992 January 22 (Box-folder 73/3)
  - Structural investigation (duplicate copy), 1992 January 22 (Box-folder 73/4)
  - Warranty deed, 1878 (Box-folder 73/5)
- Sunday School and church education, 1853-1986; Series O
  For records of Christian Education Commission, see Series B: Groups.
  For the history of the Sunday School, see Series C: History and memorabilia.
  - Transcribed notes re attendance awards, undated (Box-folder 73/6)
  - Attendance records, 1869 (Box-folder 73/7)
  - Attendance record book, 1944 September - 1945 September (Box-folder 73/8)
  - Attendance record for Sunday School Committee meetings, 1944-1969 (Box-folder 73/9)
  - Clipping re Children's Day, 1934 (Box-folder 73/10)
  - Children's Day service programs, 1898-1901; 1907 (Box-folder 73/11)
  - Children's Day service program, 1912 June 9 (Box-folder 112/21)
  - Correspondence - Note by Pastor R. F. Markham certifying that Professor M. C. King taught at Sunday School, 1890 July (Box-folder 73/12)
  - Correspondence - Letter from George H. Himes to Sunday School, 1899 May 18 (Box-folder 73/13)
    Also includes a typescript copy of the letter.
  - Correspondence - Note from Julia C. Laban to "Mr. Gilbert", 1901 December 31 (Box-folder 73/14)
  - Correspondence - Letter of appreciation to D. D. Oliphant, 1902 January 29 (Box-folder 73/15)
  - General correspondence, 1916-1926 (Box-folder 73/16)
  - Diplomas, 1906-1928 (Box-folder 113/19)
  - Robert Rakes diplomas awarded to Frank and Paul Gilbert, 1916; 1923 (Box-folder 113/20)
  - Enrollment and staff, 1946-circa 1947 (Box-folder 73/17)
  - Staff and enrollment records, 1959 October 31 (Box-folder 73/18)
  - Enrollment and attendance records, 1953; 1969-1970 (Box-folder 73/19)
  - Ephemera, circa 1915 (Box-folder 73/20)
  - "Intermediate Pupils in the Sunday School", 1936 (Box-folder 73/21)
  - "The Judson Improved Sunday School Class Book", undated (Box-folder 73/22)
    Book marked "Adults."
  - "Junior Rally Day" song lyrics, undated (Box-folder 73/23)
  - List of Sunday School superintendents, 1897-1906, circa 1906 (Box-folder 73/24)
  - Materials re Bessie Lucky's appointment as delegate at International Sunday School Convention, 1907 (Box-folder 73/25)
  - Business meetings minutes book, 1911 January - 1921 February (Box-folder 73/26)
  - Sunday School staff meeting minutes, circa 1920 (Box-folder 73/27)
  - Memorial for Harry Harper adopted by Sunday School, 1896 August 16 (Box-folder 73/28)
  - "National Series of Sunday School Lessons for 1871", 1870 (Box-folder 73/29)
  - Notes - "The Books of the Bible", undated (Box-folder 74/1)
  - Petition from Front Street Sunday School to have W. D. Scott as superintendent, circa 1906 (Box-folder 74/2)
  - Pilgrim Series, "Intermediate Quarterly", 1907 (Box-folder 74/3)
  - Promotion certificate for Anna Chenoweth, 1904 June 12 (Box-folder 74/4)
  - Records book, 1853-1864 (Box-folder 74/5)
  - Record books, 1943-1947 (Box-folder 74/6)
  - Record book, 1948 September - 1954 February (Box-folder 74/7)
  - Parent Helpers roster, 1970 (Box-folder 74/8)
  - Roster of teachers and workers, 1954 June 6 (Box-folder 74/9)
  - Staff rosters, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 74/10)
  - Teaching staff roster, 1981 (Box-folder 74/11)
  - Worship service program, 1943 February 21 (Box-folder 74/12)
  - Program for church school service, 1947 February 2 (Box-folder 74/13)
  - Youth service programs, 1966; 1971-1972; 1986 (Box-folder 74/14)
  - Teachers' textbooks, 1911, 1917 (Box-folder 74/15)
  - Toddlers classbook, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 74/16)
  - Blank workbooks, circa 1915 (Box-folder 74/17)
  - Illustrations for workbooks, 1912-1917 (Box-folder 74/18)
  - Workbook - Anna Chenoweth, "The Apostles' Creed", undated (Box-folder 74/19)
  - Workbooks of Anna Chenoweth, 1915-1918; undated (Box-folder 74/20)
  - Workbook of Virginia Fenton, circa 1915 (Box-folder 75/1)
  - Workbooks of unidentified pupils, circa 1915 (Box-folder 75/2)
- Missionary Work, circa 1895-1970; Series P
  Includes materials relating to both home missions and missionary work abroad.
  See also folders for Frances Clapp, the Dysart family, and Edwin and Alice Kellogg in Series E: Members.
  - Research files and clippings re Home Missionary work (Box-folder 75/3)
  - Research files on Missions (Box-folder 75/4)
  - Correspondence between Alta Blood and Rachel L. Hammitt re Missions, 1953 (Box-folder 75/5)
  - Mission lessons - China, circa 1895 (Box-folder 75/6)
  - "My Dollar to Help My Church Meet the World's Need" donation booklet, circa 1900 (Box-folder 75/7)
  - Document noting missionary relationship with Reverend and Mrs. Lloyd G. Van Vactor in the Philippines, 1970 April (Box-folder 75/8)
  - Vows to perform duties as trustees of Oregon Home Missionary Society, 1898, 1903-1904 (Box-folder 75/9)
- Social action, 1892-2009; Series Q
  - Research files and clippings re Social action (Box-folder 75/10)
  - AIDS candlelight vigil program, 1987 May 25 (Box-folder 75/11)
  - Alameda Center report, 1946 January 17 (Box-folder 75/12)
  - Notes re baby home and American Red Cross, circa 1918 (Box-folder 75/13)
  - Correspondence - Letter from Prohibition State Headquarters, 1892 April 15 (Box-folder 75/14)
  - Correspondence - Thank-you letter for donation to Florence Crittenton Refuge Home, 1899 March 3 (Box-folder 75/15)
  - Letters and notices re social action, 1932-1955 (Box-folder 75/16)
  - Correspondence re foreign aid donations, 1953, undated (Box-folder 75/17)
  - Correspondence - Letter from Bradley-Angle House, Inc., 1993 September (Box-folder 75/18)
  - Correspondence with Burnside Advocacy Group (BAG), 1995 (Box-folder 75/19)
  - Correspondence - Letter from Alison Wiley re energy stewardship, 2005 February 25 (Box-folder 75/20)
  - Donations by children of First Congregational Church to Heifer Project, 1998, 2000 (Box-folder 75/21)
  - Correspondence and records re Eat Pye program, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 75/22)
  - Clippings and articles re Eat Pye Program, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 75/23)
  - Correspondence and records re emergency shelter, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 75/24)
  - Correspondence and records re emergency shelter, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 75/25)
  - Clipping re English tutoring program held at First Congregational Church, 2009 April (Box-folder 75/26)
  - Brochure for Goose Hollow Family Shelter, circa 2000 (Box-folder 75/27)
  - Notes on history of social activism at First Congregational Church, circa 1997 (Box-folder 75/28)
  - Clippings re homelessness (Box-folder 75/29)
  - Open and Affirming Status, Subseries 1
    - Clippings and articles re status as Open and Affirming Church, 1987-2007 (Box-folder 75/30)
    - "Basic Writes", 2004 April (Box-folder 75/31)
    - Brochures and flyers re status as Open and Affirming Church, circa 1992-2000 (Box-folder 75/32)
    - Calendar for "Moving Towards Openness" class, circa 1996 (Box-folder 75/33)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1991-2005 (Box-folder 75/34)
    - Covenant of Openness and Affirmation, 1992, 2003 (Box-folder 75/35)
    - Gay Pride Parade, 1993, 1995 (Box-folder 75/36)
    - Opposition to Measure 9, 1992 (Box-folder 76/1)
      May also possibly include materials relating to a similar ballot measure in 2000 with the same number.
    - Press release re decision to become and Open and Affirming Church, 1992 January (Box-folder 76/2)
    - Questionnaire, 1991 October 9 (Box-folder 76/3)
    - Resolutions, 1991, undated (Box-folder 76/4)
    - Sermons, 1991, circa 1991, 2006 (Box-folder 76/5)
    - "The Wedding Celebration" program, 2004 March 21 (Box-folder 76/6)
    - Welcome sign, undated (Box-folder 76/7)
  - Peace Plebiscite, 1935 (Box-folder 76/8)
    Primarily transcripts of newspaper clippings on the subject.
  - Emergency Peace Campaign, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 76/9)
  - Clipping re Rally to Forgive Third World Debt, 2000 (Box-folder 76/10)
  - Brochure for Transition Projects, Inc., circa 2009 (Box-folder 76/11)
  - "Ways to Get Involved", circa 1990 (Box-folder 76/12)
  - Women in Community Service (WICS), circa 1995-2004 (Box-folder 76/13)
- Newsletters, 1891-2015; Series R
  All issues of "The Pilgrim" from 1929 to 1963 are compiled in bound volumes.
  For newsletters published by church committees and clubs, see Series B: Groups.
  - "Calendar" issues, 1891-1893 (Box-folder 77/1)
  - "Announcements" and "Calendar" issues, 1895 (Box-folder 77/2)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1896 January-August (Box-folder 77/3)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1896 September-December (Box-folder 77/4)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1896 September - 1897 September (Box-folder 77/5)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1896 September - 1899 January (Box-folder 77/6)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1897 January-March (Box-folder 77/7)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1897 April-June (Box-folder 77/8)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1897 July-September (Box-folder 77/9)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1897 October-December (Box-folder 77/10)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1897 September - 1899 January (Box-folder 77/11)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1898 January-March (Box-folder 78/1)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1898 April-June (Box-folder 78/2)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1898 July-September (Box-folder 78/3)
  - "The Church Record" issues, 1898 October-December (Box-folder 78/4)
  - "The Church Record"/"Calendar" issues, 1899 (Box-folder 78/5)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1900 (Box-folder 78/6)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1901 (Box-folder 78/7)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1902 (Box-folder 78/8)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1903 January-March (Box-folder 78/9)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1903 April-June (Box-folder 78/10)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1903 July-December (Box-folder 78/11)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1904 January-April (Box-folder 78/12)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1904 May-December (Box-folder 79/1)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1905 (Box-folder 79/2)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1906 (Box-folder 79/3)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1907 (Box-folder 79/4)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1907 October 6 - 1909 September 26 (Box-folder 79/5)
    Two bound volumes.
  - "Calendar" issue for week of May 22, 1910, 1910 May 22 (Box-folder 79/6)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1910 October 2 - 1912 September 29 (Box-folder 79/7)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1912 October 6 - 1914 September 27 (Box-folder 80/1)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1915 October 3 - 1916 September 24 (Box-folder 80/2)
  - "Calendar" issues, 1916 October 1 - 1917 September 30 (Box-folder 80/3)
  - "Calendar" issue for December 30, 1917, 1917 December 30 (Box-folder 80/4)
    Written in memoriam of Reverend Luther R. Dyott.
  - "The Calendar" issues, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 80/5)
  - "Calendar"/"The Calendar" issues, 1919 October 5-1921 (Box-folder 81/1)
  - "The Calendar" issues, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 81/2)
  - "The Calendar" issue for week of November 12, 1922, 1922 November 12 (Box-folder 81/3)
    Issue is missing from bound volume in 81/2
  - "The Calendar" issues, 1923-1925 (Box-folder 81/4)
  - "The Calendar" issues, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 82/1)
  - "The Calendar" issues, 1927-1929 (Box-folder 82/2)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volume 1, 1929 July 7 - 1930 June 12 (Box-folder 82/3)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volumes 2-3, 1930 September 4 - 1932 September 4 (Box-folder 82/4)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volumes 4-5, 1932 September 4 - 1934 July 29 (Box-folder 83/1)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volumes 6-7, 1934 September 4 - 1936 August 30 (Box-folder 83/2)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volumes 8-9, 1936 September 3 - 1938 August 28 (Box-folder 83/3)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volumes 10-11, 1938 September 4 - 1940 September 8 (Box-folder 83/4)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volumes 12-13, 1940 September 12 - 1942 August 31 (Box-folder 84/1)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volumes 14-15, 1942 September 10 - 1944 September 7 (Box-folder 84/2)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volumes 16-17, 1944 September 14 - 1946 September 8 (Box-folder 84/3)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volume 18, 1946 September 12 - 1947 September 7 (Box-folder 84/4)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volume 19, 1947 September 11 - 1948 September 5 (Box-folder 85/1)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volume 20, 1948 September 5 - 1949 August 28 (Box-folder 85/2)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volume 21, 1949 September 1 - 1950 August 29 (Box-folder 85/3)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volume 22, 1950 September 7 - 1951 September 2 (Box-folder 85/4)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volume 23, 1951 September 6 - 1952 August 31 (Box-folder 85/5)
  - "The Pilgrim" Volume 24, 1952 September 4 - 1953 August 30 (Box-folder 86/1)